Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-xuan-binh-19b989157 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

React Angular JavaScript

Nguyen Xuan Binh

Software Engineer - FE at SAI Digital. Ho Chi Minh City, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Hello everyone!

Welcome to my profile. I'm a Front-end Web Developer who love to learning new technologies and applying to work. I like to push myself into new challenges so I can gain new experiences and improve my skills better than before.

With more than 3 years of experiences, I have good knowledge about e-commerce and CRM (Customer Relationship Management) development. I also know a little bit of web server development and UI/UX design too.

Feel free to contact me if you want to talk about programing, technologies and communications.

Programing skills:

React | Angular | Javascript | Google scripts

Software skills:

Magento 2 | Wordpress | Google Workspace (G Suite)

Experience

SAI Digital

Software Engineer - FE

December 2021 - Present (3 years 4 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Participate in outsource team to develop web app based on customer's requirements
- Participate in product team to develop, deploy and maintain company's product web apps using Angular 2+.
- Support other team projects to keep up with deadlines.
- Research new technologies for development process.

- Develop complex web app with role hierarchy UI, dynamic table and Excel likes features

Freelance

Programing Teacher
April 2021 - May 2023 (2 years 2 months)

- Teaching website development focus on Javascript

Mekenstore

Web Developer

September 2019 - May 2023 (3 years 9 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Design website using Woocommerce
- Deploy website on the server
- Maintain website with latest technologies
- Add and update product from customer's product list

Base Business Solutions Corp.

Frontend Web Developer

April 2019 - November 2021 (2 years 8 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Participate in CRM web app development using ReactJS
- Design and deploy company's intranet using tools from Google Workspace
- Design UI and maintain company's supporting for work modules using Google Scripts and Google Workspace

Wiki Solution

Frontend Web Developer

January 2018 - March 2019 (1 year 3 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Connect directly with customers to receive latest requirements
- Maintain website using Magento 2
- Customize themes to fit customer's requirements using Magento 2

Education

Sai Gon University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering